

FERRY ANDESKA

DATA ANALYST E FRONT-END DEVELOPER

O PROFILE

Hi! I am 26 years old. I am currently working as a Data Analyst at IndiHome. I analyze everything about myIndiHome, like install & uninstall user, Active users, User behavior, Rating, User reviews, Find flaws, Development / improvement ideas and service interruption tickets.

O CONTACT

- ferryandeska23@gmail.com
- **3** 0812-9877-1542
- cileungsi, Bogor.
- fandeska.github.io

(INTEREST

- Sport
- :::: Technologies
- ★ Travelling
- Reading



EMPLOYMENT -

July 2018 - Present
PT Infomedia Solusi Humanika

Data Analyst

as a Data Analyst at IndiHome. My job is to analyze performance of myIndiHome (Indihome Mobile Application).

December 2015 - July 2018
PT Generasi Digital Internasional (GDILab.com)
Data Entry Specialist

As a Person in Charge (PIC) of Data Entry Team at GDILab.com, specification as Quality Control Data for database systems.

September 2015 - November 2015
Bank Tabungan Negara (BTN)
Funding Officer

Duty to find new customers to open an account bank and savings.



EDUCATION

2014 - 2015

Gunadarma University

Bachelor Degree of Computer Science

Computer of Science - Information Systems GPA: 3.05

2010 - 2013

Gunadarma University

Diploma Degree of Computer Science

Computer of Science - Informatics Management GPA: 2.98



SKILLS















